localsexting.com 2019-05-14

# LocalSexting.com - Sex Chat with Kik, SnapChat, Skype Contacts

1.1 Stelivo, LLC doing business as LocalSexting.com (collectively “LS” or “us” or “our” or “we”) is the owner and operator of website (“Website”) and any related sub-domains (the “Service”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) applies to the Service in its entirety but does not apply to entities that LS does not own or control. 

1.2 LS is committed to the privacy and protection of information provided to us by our users. This includes any information provided to us through our Service, including any information submitted to us through various forms and through other mechanisms. By using our Service you are accepting the privacy practices contained in this Policy. 

1.3 The purpose of our Privacy Policy is to inform our users regarding the information that we collect, utilize, and share. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or our practices in general, please contact us using the contact information provided below:  Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) 

2.1 Information Collected: there are various types of information that LS collects about you when you register with, interact with, or otherwise use our Service. Some of this information is provided voluntarily by you and other information is provided through automated processes under LS’ control. 

2.2 Information Provided By You: in addition to personally identifiable information (“PII”) provided during the LS registration process (e.g. name, address, birthday, gender, etc.), you may also provide us PII during the following non-exhaustive list of representative classes of interactions on our Service: 

  1. sharing information such as photos, videos, status updates, etc.;
  2. adding friends;
  3. signing up for private chat rooms;
  4. requesting customer support and sending LS similar communications;
  5. making payments to LS for various offerings;
  6. signing up for LS email alerts, newsletters, and similar special offers;
  7. responding to LS surveys and other special information requests; and
  8. communicating with LS regarding our compliance with applicable law.

2.3 Information Provided By Others: your friends on our Service may also provide information about you that we collect, such as: 

  1. adding you as a friend;
  2. posting on your wall;
  3. sending you a message; and
  4. otherwise interacting with you via functionality that we currently have or may add to our Service going forward.

2.4 Information Provided Automated Processes: LS may automatically collect non-PII pertaining to you when you use our Service including, but not limited to, when you use our Service via mobile and other access devices. LS may use cookies, web beacons, log files and similar methods to collect non-PII: 

  1. Cookies: a cookie is data stored in a small text file on your local access device that contains data about you. The information in the cookie is used to uniquely identify you and other users of our Service. The cookie may contain a token linked to our databases in order to provide you an enhanced feature set. It identifies a particular user at a particular point in time. You have the option of resetting your browser to reject cookies. If you choose to do so some Service functionality may not be available to you;
  2. Beacons: a web beacon is used to enable communications with third parties. It is a small image in an HTML page with all dimensions set to one (1) pixel. Because of its insignificant size, it is not visible. It is used to pass certain non-PII anonymously to third-party sites, usually advertisers;
  3. Logs: a log file is a system created file that captures certain interactions between you and our Service.

2.5 Non-PII Reservation of Rights: LS reserves the right to adopt alternative methods for collecting non-PII consistent with the provisions of this Policy and without providing further notification to you, other than what is contained herein. 

3.1 Consent Regarding Data Storage and Transfer: your use of our Service implies your consent to have your PII and non-PII (“Data”) (i.e. any Data provided by you to LS via our Service or through other mechanisms) stored, transferred and processed within the United States, or in any other country in which LS or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By providing us with your Data and using our Service you consent to any such transfer of Data outside of your country of origin, in LS’ sole discretion. 

3.2 Control and Access to Data: LS respects both the need for you to control your Data and our users’ need for sharing it with us. LS is diligent in ensuring that it has implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to prevent the unauthorized or unlawful use of your Data, and to prevent any accidental loss, destruction, or damage to such information. 

3.3  LS will use its best technical efforts to strip all geo-location meta data embedded in pictures you may upload to our Service prior to posting them to the general public. However, LS makes no guarantee as to the accuracy of this process. 

3.4 LS will allow collection of information about your general location only if you choose to make that information available via an opt-in option provided by our service 

3.5 Use of Data Collected: LS is the sole owner of the Data (i.e. as represented by the aggregate content and arrangement of the information collected about you on our Service) and will not sell, rent or share the information collected in a manner that differs from what is disclosed in this Policy. LS collects this information in order to: 

  1. accomplish the objectives of our Service;
  2. provide you with a high quality user experience on our Service;
  3. offer you a personalized feature set on our Service; and
  4. to improve our Service.

3.5 Sharing of Data in General: PII provided by you will not be shared with third parties, without your permission, for any purpose other than those enumerated below. LS, in its sole discretion, reserves the right to share with third parties aggregated non-PII for the purpose of compiling information that is relevant to our business interests. LS, in its sole discretion, reserves the right to disclose any information that it obtains through our Service to appropriate governmental or regulatory authorities or governmental agencies, if required by law. LS, in its sole discretion, may share any information collected, stored and processed, if it has a good faith belief that to do so is reasonably necessary to: 

  1. enforce our Terms of Use;
  2. detect, investigate and otherwise address fraud, security or technical breaches or related matters; or
  3. protect against imminent harm to the rights, property, or safety of LS, its users, or the public at large, as required or permitted by law.

3.6 Sharing of Payment Data: LS may share transaction information with our third party payment processor (“Payment Processor”) when you make purchases on our Service. The information shared with our Payment Processor is limited to the information required by our Payment Processor to complete the payment transaction. LS does not capture or store the financial information provided by you to our Payment Processor. LS only stores the results of said transactions as provided via notifications from our Payment Processor to us upon the completion of a payment transaction. 

3.7 Sharing of Data with Other Third Parties: in addition to disclosing information to our Payment Processor, LS may disclose your personal information to other third-party service providers (“Providers”) who perform services on our behalf. Examples of such Providers may include, but are not limited to, data storage and web hosting companies, as well as consultants we may engage for various reasons. LS requires Providers to use and protect your personal information consistent with the provisions of this Policy. 

3.8 Information You Choose to Share: through our “Privacy Settings” option you have granular control over the kinds of information that you elect to share within our Service or with the public at large. By default, your profile information is shared openly with your Friends within our Service and with the public. Our Service provides you the option to share information within your profile narrowly or widely, depending exclusively on the sharing options that you choose. 

3.9 Information Others Choose to Share: other users on our Service are free to share information in a manner consistent with their own preferences. You have no control over the manner in which others choose to share information. Therefore, information that you post, update, or otherwise contribute to our Service may be shared with others on our Service, or with the public at large, depending on the privacy options selected by other users. By using our Service you expressly acknowledge and consent that information about you may be shared in this manner. 

4.1 Any information sent by you to LS through Internet e-mail or through our Service may not be secure and is therefore done on a non-confidential basis and at your own risk. Once such information is received, LS takes appropriate security safeguards to prevent its unauthorized use, alteration, disclosure or destruction. These safeguards include periodic review of our internal processes, and benchmarking of same with industry best practices. 

4.2 Access to PII is restricted to LS employees, contractors, and agents on a need to know basis. Such individuals are generally bound by confidentiality agreements and may be subject to termination and criminal prosecution should they fail to comply as required by said agreements and/or with the contents of this Policy. 

5.1 LS processes PII only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with the provisions in this Policy. Reasonable steps are taken to ensure the quality of the PII that LS collects, processes, and stores. LS depends on its users to keep their PII current and accurate. LS conducts periodic reviews to ensure that only the PII required by our Service is captured and used consistent with the provisions of this Policy. The maintenance of data integrity is a joint collaborative effort between LS and our users. 

5.2 LS may delete data, from time to time, upon the request of an individual user. LS requires that a user present proper credentials for authentication before honoring all such requests. Good faith attempts are made to work with individual users regarding data related issues. LS reserves the right to refuse such requests when they prove unduly burdensome and/or are impractical. LS will not delete data required to be kept by applicable law or data otherwise required by LS for legitimate business reasons. 

6.1 Should LS decide to use PII other than for the purpose originally collected, LS will do so only with your consent. You will be given the opportunity to opt out of any such use. Should LS become involved in a sale, acquisition, or any form of transfer of some or all of its assets, then LS will provide notice to you before your PII is subject to a new or different privacy policy. 

6.2 You always have the option of contacting LS should you have questions regarding your PII. Please contact LS using the contact information provided above. 

7.1 LS restricts the use of our Service to individuals of legal age eighteen (18) years old and older. LS does not knowingly collect or solicit PII from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent of a child under the age of 18 and you suspect that your child has registered on our Service, then you can request that any information provided be immediately deleted from LS’ database(s) by sending an email to: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or by contacting LS via the contact information provided above. LS will promptly respond to any such notification, and upon verification, immediately delete the information in question. 

7.2 No one under the age of 18 should attempt to register on our Service, or otherwise provide LS any PII including name, email address, phone number, physical address or any similar information. The protection of children on the Internet is an important public policy concern—one that LS is committed to supporting. 

Our Service may contain hyperlinks to third-party websites that may collect or solicit information. Our Privacy Policy does not cover information collected or solicited by these third-party websites. LS is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. LS users are encouraged to pay attention when they leave our Service and to read the respective privacy policies of each website that collects personally identifiable information. This Policy only applies to information provided by you to LS via our Service or through other mechanisms. 

Because we are committed to protecting our users’ PII, LS conducts periodic reviews of our internal processes to ensure that we remain in compliance with this Policy. We will cooperate with the appropriate authorities to resolve any user complaints regarding the transfer of PII. LS will initially try to resolve the complaint with the individual user. Formal complaints should be sent to LS using the contact information provided above. 

In the future, we may make changes to our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our privacy practices and/or changes to our Service. LS’ goal is to keep our users aware of what information we collect, use, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. When changes are made to this Policy the “last updated date” will be modified accordingly. If changes are made to our Privacy Policy then LS will provide notification on our Website. In addition, further notification will be provided to users that have registered with our Service.
